<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<story>
<scene1>
  <jeebus>Ow. Where am I?</jeebus>
  <god>Yo kid!</god>
  <jeebus>Hey, papa. What happened to me?</jeebus>
  <god>Don’t you remember? You got yo’ ass busted by some guys with eyepatches and tophats.</god>
  <jeebus>Nope. Can't recall a thing.</jeebus>
  <god>Were you drinking too? It’s not like it’s the first time it happened to you. Get up on your feet. You have work to do.</god>
  <jeebus>Like what?</jeebus>
  <god>Hommie, it’s easter! Your job was actually to get beaten and get here. You gotta like, open the hell gates, man and free those noobs, umm... I mean innocent people!</god>
  <jeebus>Okay, and how am I supposed to do this?</jeebus>
  <god>I don’t know, man. Not my problem. Figure it out.</god>
  <jeebus>Come on, you are almighty. You should know that.</jeebus>
  <god>Me dammit! Fine. If I am not wrong, and I can’t be wrong, you have to fight those thugs who got you here, and then you will be able to get to the gates.</god>
  <jeebus>Well, that sounds easy enough.</jeebus>
  <god>Just like your mother.</god>
  <jeebus>Screw you dad.</jeebus>
  <god>Like I did your mom?</god>
  <jeebus>Are you for real?</jeebus>
   <god>Ahem. Anyay, get the job done now or no dinner for you.</god>
</scene1>
<scene2>
  <bb>What’s up, Doc?</bb>
  <jeebus>Yo, Bugs! I am here to open the hell gates. What about you?</jeebus>
  <bb>I’m afraid I can’t let you do that, Jeebie. I am here to stop you from doing this.</bb>
  <jeebus>Butt why? Thought we were buddies!</jeebus>
  <bb>I represent all the bunnies in this world who are neglected every easter because of your resurrection. Who the hell dies every year anyway?</bb>
  <jeebus>Hey, it’s not my fault. My padre made me do this. Besides that, all the kids love you, not me. You are the one who brings them candies. They even make chocolate bunnies and not a single chocolate Jeebus.</jeebus>
  <bb>Enough blabbering. Get rekt, scrub.</bb>
  <jeebus>gr8 b8 m8, i r8 it 8/8. can’t w8 to desintegr8 you.</jeebus>
</scene2>
<scene3>
  <jeebus>'Kay dad. I just killed bugs bunny and I'm ready to open the gates.</jeebus>
  <god>You killed what?!</god>
  <jeebus>Umm... long story. Anyway, I'm done here, can I go back now?</jeebus>
  <god>Well, I guess you did good. You're still not going home yet though.</god>
  <jeebus>What do you mean I'm not going home? I did my job perfectly!</jeebus>
  <god>Well, you gotta go back to earth in three days. Until then, find something fun to do around there. Gotta go now. Sayonara, mio figlio!</god>
  <jeebus>I hate you so much.</jeebus>    
  <end>Congratulations, you opened the hellgates and saved Easter. We hope you liked our game, and thanks for playing!</end>
  </scene3>
</story>